(Bernadette:)Excuse me, I need to have a chat
with my husband.
Well, now, keep it short.
(Sheldon:)From what I gather,
brevity is your friend.
(Sheldon:)So, are we good here?
(Amy:)No, we're not good here.
I am working on this project.
Yeah, you can't tell her
what she can and cannot do.
(Sheldon:)Last week, you told Leonard
he couldn't wear
(Sheldon:)his Wookie jacket out in public.
(Penny:)That's different.
I'm not going to the mall
(Penny:)with someone dressed
like a dumb space bear.
(Amy:)Sheldon, you don't have to worry
about me bothering you.
(Amy:)I'll be in a different building,
(Amy:)and we don't even have
to have lunch together.
(Sheldon:)-Really?
-Yes.
(Amy:)Before all things, I'm a scientist.
(Amy:)I'm just there to do my work
and, with a little luck,
(Amy:)scare the living crap
out of some monkeys.
(Sheldon:)Hmm.
(Sheldon:)You sure your moth-like personality
won't be drawn
(Sheldon:)to this blazing fire that is myself?
(Amy:)More and more sure.